D2.
Read Kitty's article about her best friend.
My best friend.
My best friend is Joan.
I met her at a dance club five years ago.
Joan is taller than me.
Her hair is long and soft.
I like her bright smiling eyes.
They make her look pretty and kind.
Joan is helpful and patient.
Sometimes I cannot do well in our dance class and she is always kind to give me help.
Joan is caring and thoughtful.
I often tell her when something worries me and she always tries to help and keeps it secret.
Joan is also a cheerful person.
She likes to look on the bright side.
Every time I feel down she will cheer me up.
I think Joan is great and I hope we will be best friends forever.